{"data":[{"question":"A man has a right to spend his money ___ he pleases.","a":"how","b":"in which","c":"why","d":"for which","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Where refers to place \n- Why refers to reason \n- How refers to means\/method or way to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"She was rich,___ unfortunately I was not.","a":"that","b":"what","c":"which","d":"who","answer":"3","explain":"\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person. \n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n+ What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"The doctor told me to take a few days' rest, ___ advice I did not follow.","a":"that","b":"what","c":"this","d":"which","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Which: used, after a comma in writing, to add more information about the thing, situation, or event you have just mentioned","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"___ business you may be engaged in, you must do your best.","a":"Whatever","b":"However","c":"Whoever","d":"Wherever","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Whatever: used to say that it is not important what happens, what you do etc because it does not change the situation \n- However: in whatever way \n- Whoever: used to say that it does not matter who does something, is in a particular place etc \n- Wherever: to or at any place, position, or situation","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"___ clever you may be, you will not make out the meaning.","a":"Whichever","b":"Whoever","c":"However","d":"Wherever","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Whichever: used to say that it does not matter which thing or person is chosen because the result will be the same \n- However: used to say that it does not matter how big, good, serious etc something is because it will not change a situation in any way [= no matter how] \n- Whoever: used to say that it does not matter who does something, is in a particular place etc \n- Wherever: to or at any place, position, or situation","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"You may come ___ it is convenient to you.","a":"however","b":"whenever","c":"wherever","d":"whatever","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Whenever: at any time \n- However: used to say that it does not matter how big, good, serious etc something is because it will not change a situation in any way [= no matter how] \n- Whatever: used to say that it is not important what happens, what you do etc because it does not change the situation \n- Wherever: to or at any place, position, or situation","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"You can not succeed without perseverance,___ you may go.","a":"whenever","b":"whatever","c":"however","d":"wherever","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Whenever: at any time \n- However: used to say that it does not matter how big, good, serious etc something is because it will not change a situation in any way [= no matter how] \n- Whatever: used to say that it is not important what happens, what you do etc because it does not change the situation \n- Wherever: to or at any place, position, or situation","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Rice is to the Chinese ___ potatoes are to many Europeans.","a":"whose","b":"that","c":"what","d":"which","answer":"3","explain":"- What + clause: object clause","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"___ working too hard and taking too little care of himself, he was taken ill.","a":"The thing that","b":"What is","c":"That which is with","d":"What with","answer":"4","explain":"\n- What: used at the beginning of a statement to emphasize what you are going to say","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"___ might have been expected, he refused our request.","a":"What","b":"As","c":"That which","d":"Which","answer":"2","explain":"\n- As: used to say that what you are saying is already known or has been stated before","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}